infibeam.com 2009-06-09

# Privacy Policy

#### Collection of Information

If you browse through this site without providing us with any personal information, we will gather and store some information about your visit, such as IP address, type of browser and operating system used, date and time you access our site, pages you visit, and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website. This information will not identify you personally and will not be linked back to you. 

There will be times, such as when you submit an auto lead request to a dealer or fill out our contact form, when we will need to obtain personally identifiable information from you or about you. Such personally identifiable information may include your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and identification number. 

#### Use and Sharing of Information

At no time will we sell your personally-identifiable data without your permission unless set forth in this Privacy Policy. The information we receive about you or from you may be used by us or shared by us with our corporate affiliates, dealers, agents, vendors and other third parties to help process your request; to comply with any law, regulation, audit or court order; to help improve our website or the products or services we offer; for research; to better understand our customers' needs; to develop new offerings; and to alert you to new products and services (of us or our business associates) in which you may be interested. We may also combine information you provide us with information about you that is available to us internally or from other sources in order to better serve you. 

We do not share, sell, trade or rent your personal information to third parties for unknown reasons.

#### Cookies

From time to time, we may place "cookies" on your personal computer. "Cookies" are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also, our site uses cookies to track how you found our site. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies certain features of the site may not function property or at all as a result. 

#### Links

Our website contains links to other sites. Such other sites may use information about your visit to this website. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to practices of such sites that we do not own or control or to people we do not employ. Therefore, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the accuracy or the integrity of the content included on such other sites. We encourage you to read the individual privacy statements of such websites.

#### Security

We safeguard your privacy using known security standards and procedures and comply with applicable privacy laws. Our websites combine industry-approved physical, electronic and procedural safeguards to ensure that your information is well protected though it's life cycle in our infrastructure.

Sensitive data is hashed or encrypted when it is stored in our infrastructure. Sensitive data is decrypted, processed and immediately re-encrypted or discarded when no longer necessary. We host web services in audited data centers, with restricted access to the data processing servers. Controlled access, recorded and live-monitored video feeds, 24/7 staffed security and biometrics provided in such data centers ensure that we provide secure hosting.

#### Opt-Out Policy

Please email [privacy@infibeam.net](mailto:privacy@infibeam.net) if you no longer wish to receive any information from us. 

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Our privacy policy was last updated on September 1, 2007. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do, we will update this Privacy Policy on our website.

#### Questions

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail your questions to us at [privacy@infibeam.net](mailto:privacy@infibeam.net)
